Hey everyone! Today I'm going to show you five different looks with this face mask.
Clubs are closed, I can't go out partying anymore, so I thought let's do some cool
looks just for the fun of it and I hope you're going to like them. This face mask
is from Reagenz. I really like it because of the slightly futuristic look and I
had a bit of trouble shooting this video. Yesterday I wanted to do it outdoors
then it started to rain so I switched to in-rows but I think some outfits are
just way cooler shown outside.
Let's go!
Thank you.
Alright, that was it.
take this outfit too serious now at least I know what I'm going to wear if
I'm invited to a wedding soon. No, I had fun creating these looks I hope you had
fun as well watching me present these looks and stay safe take care and see
you around